Alright, the muss db
D
I'm going to be a little bit more careful.
shooting that and then
the
first
an
and
Two
two
three
and
we
Living on us through the land Trapped in our peak, it's a pain
I've won a man so comfortable living in a Bible, Bible
Haunted lonely, I'm bearing a trouble
Bearing, when the land will never be enough
I'm falling on, we're comfortable living in a Bible, Bible, Bible
I'm falling on, we're comfortable living in a Bible
So smile, your face kinda glasses on And I'm done, yeah, move on
Come on, can you put your hands together for me?
Yeah, we're living with you, dreamin' the thoughts on me
We're all changed to the riddle, to the riddle
Dreamin' up, it's your baby's home, dance and dance
Dreamin' up, keep it on baby, somebody around the waist, dreams on me
Yeah, we're living with you, dreamin' this once on me
I'm over, I'm over, I'm over
How we don't live, keep swimming in under the mud
I'm weaker, too better, and I'm over, we can't
So comfortable living in a Bible, Bible, Bible, Bible
So smile, your face kinda glasses on And I'm done, yeah, move on
Come on, can you put your hands together for me?
Yeah, we're living with you, dreamin' this once on me
We're all changed to the riddle, to the riddle
Dreamin' up, it's your baby's home, dance and dance
How you feeling, my boy?
I'm so happy to be here tonight
Are you happy to be here tonight?
That's good, one night in my body
Come on, dance and dance
Dreamin' up, somebody around
Yeah, we think we're free, dreamin' this once on me
We're all changed to the riddle
Let's go!
Move on, move on, move on
Move on, move on
Oh, it goes
Move on, move on, move on
Oh, move, move on, move on
Change, change, change, change
You've waited long enough, so you deserve to hear every single song that you love
You ready?
I knew you were, you were gonna come to bed
Yeah, you are
But your bad shoes kept in there
I'm capable of anything, of anything
And everything makes me a regrettive
Make me a regrettive
And only
Don't make me regretter me
You're an only
So you wanna play with my day
Boy, you should know what you're falling for
Baby, do you dare to do this
Cause I'm coming at you like a drug
Are you ready for the righty boy
Perfect song, perfect song
Let's watch your mind, watch your mind
What?
My poor, this level make you levitate
I know
Like a bird without a cave
Can't imagine it
If you just do walk away
Don't walk away
It's in the form of your hand
Now baby
It's a yes or no
No, baby
Just be sure
Before you give it all to me
All to me
Give it all
To me
You're an only
So you wanna play with my day
Boy, you should know what you're falling for
Baby, do you dare to do this
Cause I'm coming at you like a drug
Are you ready for the righty boy
Perfect song, perfect song
Let's watch your mind, watch your mind
What?
My poor, this level make you levitate
I know
So you wanna play with my day
Boy, you should know what you're falling for
Baby, do you dare to do this
Cause I'm coming at you like a drug
Are you ready for the righty boy
Perfect song, perfect song
Let's watch your mind, watch your mind
Take it all
Let's go
You're so hypnotizing
Could you be the devil?
Could you be an angel?
Your church, magnetizing
Feels it going floating
Lift my body glow like a base
Feel it right
You're not like the other
So you're just a lover
The day, friend, day and day
I don't understand you, you're from the world
I'm too pretty to mention
You are open for eyes
Cause I'm ready for it
Kiss me, kiss me
With your love
Tell me, where could my life be
Check to check me
Wanna be a picture
Ready for the shot
I'm a boy
You're hypnotizing
Could you be the devil?
I'm too pretty to mention
You are open for eyes
Cause I'm ready for it
You're not like the other
So you're just a lover
The day, friend, day and day
I don't understand you, you're from the world
I'm too pretty to mention
You are open for eyes
Cause I'm ready for it
You're not like the other
So you're open for eyes
Cause I'm ready for it
You're not like the other
So you're open for eyes
Cause I'm ready for it
Kiss me, kiss me
With your love
Tell me, where could my life be
Check to check me
Wanna be a picture
Ready for the shot
I'm a boy
You're not like the other
So you're open for eyes
Cause I'm a boy
You're hypnotizing
This is just a shadow
On another level
Boy, you're not like a story
I wanna walk on your way
I'll be there when you're by my way
For you are a skin of
's
siento
Feel it
I
Just
want to be a picture
Ready for the shot
I'm a boy
I'm
Canad
го
touch
an
dé
Of
commercial
HOLA
Don't touch me, don't touch me
Don't touch me, I'm in the air
I'm a star, I'm in the sky
I'm in the sky, I'm in the sky
I'm in the sky
Are you hungry, no mind
I'm in the sky, I'm in the sky
Let's see
Look, I can't tell
You got those eyes
You look good just to check
Cause your level's in bright
I'm a star, I'm in the sky
I'm a COVID-19
You want me to go get
Boy, take your lunch
I'm the candle light
We can't wind and die
A table for two
If you take your time
Eat with your hands, my eyes
I'm under the UV
It's all in your heart
Baby, I'm boy
It's red and it's my face
Well now, well now, put your baby
I'll take this election
Fresh I'll be oven
You better work your mama
I'll be the one I'm gonna put your baby
So you want some more
I'm an oven 25
But I keep you in the sky
Cause your mother's always right
I hope you got some room
For the sweetest tonight
Gonna hit that sweet tooth
Boy, I'm under the candle light
We can't wind and die
A table for two
If you take your time
Eat with your hands, my eyes
I'm under the UV
It's all in your heart
I'm bright and it's my face
No, I'm not
One ball, let me see who gives
Come on, let me see who gives
Who's gonna give 20
Come on, let's go
Come on
I'm gonna put your baby
Let's do a little
A little chanel Jackson
Anybody want some chanel Jackson?
Let's go
We're happy
You just want me, let me see who gives
One of the two of you
We're happy, you just want me, let me see who gives
We're happy
You just want me, let me see who gives
Awesome, no?
One of the two of you
Mumbai, you are so swaddily out
Come on
What's up?
Here's the end
You ready to have some fun tonight?
What about all we hear is your ready to have some fun tonight?
This is how we do it
It's Friday night and I feel all right
The 40s here on the west side
So I reach for my 40 and I turn it up
There's a knitted diver take the keys to my truck
With the shock as I'm faded
Honey's in the street saying money, oh we made it
If it's so good, then we're happy
You just want me to be happy
You just want me, let me see who gives
berries
When it's all I need
Oh
That's all we do it
Come on by
How do you feel right here
All the way up there
In the bleachers
Anybody out there watching the show tonight
I'm about to
But I'm wondering if I can be a two-inch green
Oh
Who's my teenage dream
That's
Oh
Tonight in Mumbai
So
Hey
I am Katie Perry
And I am told that this is your winter
Oh my
Goddess
You know what you've been cheering for me
But I think
Knowing how much it takes to come together in a place like this the money the hours the traffic the heat you should give
Yourself's a round of applause
Listen we love you
That's why we're here is because we never want to forget you
It's been seven years since I was last in India
I can't believe myself
Like look at how many people showed up
Mumbai
From all over
So maybe it's not going to be another seven years right
But you know what
I got to dedicate this next song
To all of you
That have been following me
Since one of the boys
And if you don't know what that is that is my very first record
And this song
Hopefully will
Cool you off
Or maybe it'll just heat you back up
Let's go
You
Change your mind like a girl
Changes holes
The end you
Be a mess like a bitch
I would know
And you
Of a fake
Always speak
Cryptically
I should know
They are
Oh
Cryptically
Cause you're
I know
No
You know
Nothing is wrong
I can't
Really
But you're not
I'm gonna hold you, hold you, hold you, hold you, hold you, hold you, hold you, hold you, hold you, hold you, hold you, hold you, hold you, hold you, hold you, hold you, hold you, hold you, hold you, hold you, hold you, hold you, hold you, hold you, hold you, hold you, hold you, hold you, hold you, hold you, hold you, hold you, hold you, hold you, hold you, hold you, hold you, hold you, hold you, hold you, hold you, hold you, hold you, hold you, hold you, hold you, hold you, hold you, hold you, hold you, hold you, hold you, hold you, hold you, hold you, hold you, hold you, hold you, hold you, hold you, hold you, hold you, hold you, hold you, hold you, hold you, hold you, hold you, hold you, hold you, hold you, hold you, hold you, hold
hold you let's go, hold you, hold you, hold you, hold you, hold you, hold
Sing on the go, in the go out, open your mouth
And I'm one, one, two, none there
Gotta keep my love high, pull it
It's a corner, full of culture
You can't get it all this bright
Cause you, change your mind, I could go
Girl, you look jackal and you look good and not just
ật
Oh, look at that.
This Saturday night.
How are we gonna do it all again?
One by one.
This Saturday, let's go.
Two, three, four.
Three, four, three, four.
That's a long way.
I love you too.
So has anyone ever been to California?
It's kind of far away, right?
Actually, my body says you should be asleep right now.
So I'm gonna need you to make some freaking noise.
I'm gonna pay snacks.
One by one.
Then my personality in the world.
Sit back and turn the juice.
Lay it on and need the palm trees.
Boys, break their necks.
Tryna creep a little sleepy.
You can turn the world.
Another guy's close to the coldest guy.
You'll be fine with her.
Counting four girls were unforgettable.
Daisy, doomspricinis on top.
Sunkisskin's so hot, we'll munch your popsicles.
See?
Counting four girls were under nine for fine fresh tears.
We got a lot of wet, good breath, isn't it?
Don't put your hands up.
Sex.
I beat with that mindset, I still am old.
We're free in my cheeks.
So knock it down on the stairs.
You can trouble the way.
Another guy's close to the coldest guy.
You ready for mine?
Let's go.
Counting four girls were unforgettable.
Daisy, doomspricinis on top.
Sunkisskin's so hot, we'll munch your popsicles.
Counting four girls were under nine for fine fresh tears.
We got a lot of wet, good breath, isn't it?
Don't put your hands up.
Come on, team.
Turn it up.
I'm gonna go, I'm gonna go.
You better show them.
Come on.
I'm okay.
I love that leg of thinnest speech and palm strings.
Some of the times every day, homeboys banging out.
All that ass hanging out.
Look at here, baby.
I'm on my own, because you represent in California.
We're not forgetful, baby.
Look at these eyes.
So hot, we'll munch your popsicles.
I'm not gonna go.
We're moving to nine for fine fresh tears.
We got a lot of wet, good breath, isn't it?
Don't put your hands up.
Come on, team.
Turn it up.
I'm gonna go, I'm gonna go.
You better show them.
Come on, team.
Turn it up.
Come on.
So this next song goes out to all the beautiful girls.
In Mumbai.
If you're a beautiful woman and you know it, you make some noise.
This was never the way I planned.
Not my intention.
I got silver-grave dream and hand lost.
My discretion, it's not wide.
I'm used to just wanna try you.
One, I'm your ring, eyes for you.
Come on, my attention.
I can't stand to run.
I like dead.
The taste of her cherry jabs.
I can't stand to run.
I hope my friend or mine, it's not so wrong.
It's not so right.
Don't mean I'm in love tonight.
I can't stand to run.
I like dead.
Let's take it all the way back to 2008.
Everybody!
No, I don't need any more.
In chocolate, it doesn't matter.
We all are mine, experiment again.
You and nature, it's not mine.
The truth, how they should behave.
I like it so called for you.
Take it all the way back to 2008.
I hope my friend or mine, it's not so wrong.
It's not so right.
Don't mean I'm in love tonight.
I can't stand to run.
I like it.
Because I, girls, we are so magical.
Soft skin redness.
So fricking simple.
Hard to resist.
Talk to Chippa.
Chocolate too.
And I am.
Don't mean the passing of time.
So here's a story.
I'm gonna girl the place.
Guitar.
You've been a showtime guy.
And I'm so lucky.
I'm a showtime guy.
I'm a kissie.
I like it.
Thank you.
I see you.
You see me.
Maybe I'll know.
Make some noise for Adam on the drums!
Make some noise for Cheerio, Sherry and the Indian!
Make some noise for Timmy and the Indian!
And time!
Get up from that beer and come on!
Give a light, give a OnePlus phone!
Why don't you turn the light on and we'll make this whole stadium glow!
Oh so wrong!
I know it's clear to me that everything you see ain't always what it seems
Yeah, I was dreaming for so long
I wish I knew that what I know now wouldn't dive in, wouldn't bow down
Grab that e-hurt and made it so sweet till the world got on on the concrete
But tonight I should fall high
Come on, I'm ready to go to the night
Yeah, I'm falling from the clouds tonight
I'm way away, now losing endlessly, perfect to every piece
And it all my feet, nothing to complete myself
No, I want to wake, yeah I am born again
I don't belong there, I don't have to pretend
It was too late, the show is over now the end
I wish I knew that what I know now wouldn't dive in, wouldn't bow down
Grab that e-hurt and made it so sweet till the world got on on the concrete
Oh, let it fall high
Come on, I'm ready to go to the night
I'm falling from the clouds tonight
I'm going to wake up, yeah I'm falling
Got a certain stroke, yeah I'm going to wake up, yeah I'm falling
Got a certain stroke, yeah I'm falling
I'm falling from the clouds tonight
I see you all the way up there, now with those lights, wake for me
I wish I knew that what I know now wouldn't dive in, wouldn't bow down
Grab that e-hurt and made it so sweet till the world got on on the concrete
Oh, let it fall high
Come on, I'm falling from the clouds tonight
I'm going to wake up, yeah I'm falling
I'm going to wake up, yeah I'm going to wake up
Thank you so much, Mumbai
You still having fun
Good, because I've noticed I have swallowed a couple of flies
So I feel like very one with all of you
Because every time I go to breathe, somehow a tiny little bug makes a home in my mouth
I feel like maybe that is the initiation here
Are you guys having fun?
Now it's been such an awesome day, how many of you raise your hand if you traveled for this show?
Raise your hand if you traveled two hours for this show
Me too
Raise your hand if you traveled five hours for this show
Wow, okay we're going to keep going
Raise your hand if you traveled ten hours for this show
Raise your hand if you traveled fifteen hours for this show
Make some noise if all that travel was worth it
How many of you had so much fun watching Doa Lipa?
I have a crush on Doa Lipa
Make some noise if you also have a crush on Doa Lipa
If Doa and I were together would you ship us?
Well unfortunately it's not in this lifetime
Because I have been promised to someone else
But she did set a fantastic job
And all the other bands that came today thank you so much for making the first one plus music festival a success
In fifteen years when you're all coming back and you're like oh I went to the very first one plus music festival
And everybody's like are you going to the one plus music festival this year?
Oh my god so I was playing you're like I basically started that festival
So congratulations on being a pioneer
This next song goes out to Doa Lipa it's called The One That Got Away
Should we wait for that mic?
We're just changing a battery for microphone
This is one of my backup singers her name is actually India isn't that cool?
So India is always with me
And Cherry because everything is better with the cherry on top
Summer after high school when we first met we made a new Mustang to a new head
And I'm a 18 birthed we got my dream tattoo
Don't do that
You used to steal your past liquor and come to the road
Talk about our future like we had a clue
I'll never plan the one day I'll be using you
And another life I would be a girl
We keep on promises be our second source
And another life I would make you stay
So I don't have to say we're the one that got away
The one that got away
I was doing a new work my journey cash
And I went with that the other made it pop
Sometimes when I miss you I bump over the red page on
Someone said you had your tattoo removed
You saw your downtown, saying the blues
I'm the face of music I'm no longer your muse
And another life I would be a girl
We keep on promises be our second source
And another life I would make you stay
So I don't have to say we're the one that got away
The one that got away
And all this money can buy me a time machine
No, can't replace you with a feel you're being
No, I should have told you what you meant to me
Oh, cause now I pay the price
See, and another life
I would make you stay
So I don't have to say we're the one that got away
The one that got away
The one, the one that got away
And all this money can buy me a time machine
No, I should have told you what you meant to me
So I don't have to say we're the one that got away
The one that got away
Thank you, Mumbai!
We're gonna do something
We've never done before
We're gonna sing something we've never sung before
Let's go for Harley's and Mumbai
Boy, tell me got me take my breath away
Goes and down a hard trip, highway, guide
Tristroving lane to lane, don't hit the bridge
Cause I'm feeling so safe, I'll be your baby
On a Sunday, oh I don't wake it out at town
Call me your baby on the same wave
Oh, no, no, there's no window
You and I, I ride in Harley's in Hawaii
I'm on the back of holding tight
I want you to take me for a ride
When I hold on
You sing me to the trood on trood on trood
You think I'm moving on the sky
We're riding Harley's in Hawaii
Yeah, I ride in the rain
Let me run my fingers through
You're so empty here
Go ahead and explore the island by
So really you can feel it in the air
I'm heaven up your earth down
I'll be your baby on a Sunday, oh I don't wake it out at town
Call me your baby, get your save
Oh, no, no, no, there's no window
You and I, I ride in Harley's in Hawaii
I'm on the back of holding tight
I want you to take me for a ride
When I hold on
You sing me to the trood on trood on trood
You think I'm moving on the sky
We're riding Harley's in Hawaii
Let's ride, come on
Oh, no, let's ride some Harley's in Hawaii
From, from, ready?
You and I, here you go
You and I, there you go
Go ahead and explore the island by
So really you can feel it in the air
You and I, here you go
I ride in the rain
Oh, no, no, no, there's no window
I'll be your baby on a Sunday, oh I don't wake it out
We're riding hoodies in my life
We're riding hoodies in Hawaii
We're riding hoodies in what you're showing me
Oh my god, what's the point in your mouth?
To know it, that you need found the best
That if this is now
This is the economy
That you never thought of
That's the point where I'm being
So I know this is the part
Of me, that you never thought of
That's the point where I'm being
So be a slight thing done
My heart can't go back
That you're not gonna break my dust
And I'm just the part
Of me, that you never thought of
That's the point where I'm being
So I just wanna throw my phone away
Find out who this really is, that I'm gonna be
You're gonna be the love energy, it's always good
I'm gonna cease, I'm gonna be the only child
That is the dead, it is just now
This is what I'm gonna be, it's just never done
Never take away my freedom
This is hold on, it's just stop
Listen
You want the truth?
So, I gotta tell you the frickin' truth, you guys
The real truth is, I just tried to change my costume
And I'm sweating so much, I could not
I literally tried to change my costume
And the back of my costume ripped in half
Because if you've ever tried to change in two minutes
In extreme humidity, it is a miracle
So, we're gonna start this song over because you deserve to hear it with me
You ready for it?
And I'm just gonna stay in this because I'm sweating in every crack
You sweating out there too with me?
Hell yeah, let's do it
There's no way I was getting it right
Come on
Days like this, I wanna drive away
Pack my bags and watch your shadow fade
You took me up, it's been me
All I got was poison in your mouth
You took my light, you drained me down
But that was that and this is now
Now look at me
This is the part of me that you never want
I'm never tick away from me
All your secrets are all the time
But you're not gonna break my soul
This is the part of me that you never want
I'm never tick away from me
I just wanna throw my instant ground away
And find out who doesn't even better for me
You went to meet me, all through your lower cheeks
With all the ways I've been seen
I'm feeling different than me
Drown for canvas, there and this is now
Now look at me, let's go, bye bye
This is the part of me that you never want
I'm never tick away from me
All your secrets are all the time
But you're not gonna break my soul
This is the part of me that you never want
I'm never tick away from me
I'm sparking fire, we're getting tense today
You will never put me on again, I'm alive
Are you cooking, don't worry
No, I don't be thinking any way
You fucked your cake, you everything
What?
Exhaust for me
This is the party, this is the party man
This is the party man
No, this is the party man
You're not gonna pay my debt
This is the party man
Let's go away
No
This is the party man
No, this is the party man
Don't you think this is so
Do you want to know
You're not gonna pay for
So, we're gonna never want to be
You should never wanna ever take away my gift
No!
What's that?
Listen
You still got time for a little more
Yes!
You know what?
Swishishish
Aha!
No, bye!
I'm tired
Don't lose no sleep
Don't need opinions
From a shellfish or a she-white
Don't you come for me
No, that's it
You're calculated
I got your number
Cause you are Joker
And I'm a court-signed killer queen
And you will kiss the ring
You best believe
So keep calm honey
I'm a sick girl
For more than a minute
Get used to it
Find my name
Keeps coming out your mouth
What?
Come on
Swishishish
Can't touch this
Come on, bye!
Aha!
Your game is tired
You should expire
You're not good
All you've done expires
And calm it's not a liar
Cause she keeps wrongs it
So keep calm honey
I'm a sick girl
Get used to it
Find my name
Keeps coming out your mouth
May your mouth fly
Swishishish
Come on
I heard this is one of your favorites
Can't touch this
Can't have the one in the casket
I'm number one
I don't know what
Oh, what?
I'm the don't know what it's worth
They just shout
What's up?
Will you help me sing it?
Let's go!
I'm losing myself control
Yeah
And you're starting to trickle back in
But I don't wanna fall down the rabbit hole
No
Where's my heart? I won't do it again
It's time, it's time, it's time, it's a trove
And look
And I do what to do
You're passing away
I'm in the cross of life
I think of you
Take me to the angels
My heart sometimes deeper
The hero's done for it
I'm in the rain
I'm in the sunshine
It's the colors that give the best
The one who is done for it
Let's go!
Just listen to the song of another
Peter Charlie over and he won't think it over
Maybe I'll be coming over again
I guess I could try hypnotherapy
I gotta rewire this brain right India
Cause I can't even go on the internet
You wanna talk him out?
Without him, I'm not gonna talk
I'm not gonna talk
I'm not gonna talk him out
Without even checking his name
Tell him I'm so dumb
I'm so dumb
I'm not gonna lie
And I do what to do
I'm passing the one
You're perfect
I'm just gonna lie
I think of you
Who isn't just like that?
My heart sometimes deeper
I'm in the eyes
I guess it's never really over
Singing
Just because of Summer doesn't mean that
If you're over and can think it over
Maybe you'll become over and again
You'll become over and again
Just because of Summer doesn't mean until you're over and again
I think it'll become maybe you'll become over again
I'm not gonna think it over and again
The weak is gonna fire
But we'll know this time
What's the last word?
I guess it's never really over
We do the line
Right through your window
I can't keep going back
Really over
Truth and justice
Re-show
One
wore
I'm gonna be mad at you, I'm gonna be mad at you
It's never really over
It's never really over, man
Bye!
Thank you for coming out here tonight.
Thank you for starting the one plus festival.
And I hope these next two songs, these last two songs,
re-inspire your life.
If you're looking for some inspiration, I hope this helps.
But these next two songs, these last two songs, listen,
I know a lot of you are all strangers.
You don't know each other, right?
And you came from many different places.
But I know you might know these last two songs.
So I want you to act like everyone around you is your friend.
Is your community and sing these last two songs with me?
Will you?
Because don't you feel so disconnected sometimes?
It feels like, oh, I'm on my phone all the time.
I never really go out.
I never really socialize with this big of a crowd.
Well, let's change that for these last two songs.
Are you ready to run?
Yes.
Come on.
My boy.
You're going to dance with me.
Let's hop.
I'm going to dance with you.
Come on.
Let's run, my boy.
I used to write my tongue and hold my breath.
I'm scared to run football in the mess.
So I said, quiet, hey, I'll group the line.
I guess it I forgot.
I had a choice.
I let you push me past the breaking point.
I stood for not a thing.
So I'm over everything.
You help me down, but I got up.
Oh, buddy.
You hit my boy, you let it down.
Like I'm gonna shake the world.
You help me down, but I got up.
Get ready.
I see it all, I see it now.
I got the eye of the tiger.
The tiger is dead and the fire is burning.
I'm gonna be a human.
You're gonna be a world.
I'm gonna be a fire.
I'm gonna be a world.
Now I'm going in like a butterfly.
Singing like a bee at the start.
I went from CEO to my own hero.
You help me down, but I got up.
Oh, buddy.
You hit my boy, you let it down.
Like I'm gonna shake the world.
You help me down, but I got up.
Get ready.
I see it all, I see it now.
See it?
I got the eye of the tiger.
The tiger is dead and the fire is burning.
You're gonna be a world.
I'm gonna be a fire.
I'm gonna be a world.
You're gonna be a world.
Get ready.
I'm gonna be a world.
You're gonna be a world.
Make some eyes for my dancers.
Make some eyes for me, girl.
I'll leave you with this, Mumbai.
Do you ever feel like a class of band?
Nine minutes of time, just for the night,
Like to find a world tonight.
It's for me.
Come on, show up.
You're one.
Make some eyes for my dancers.
I just shoot a curse
The sky
Baby you're fine
You're worth
Gone and you're cursed
But
It's make a goal
You're the kind of evil
Now
Oh
Let's do this one all together yeah my boy
Thank you so much
You don't have to feel like always in space
You're original
Cannot be replaced
If you want me new
What the future holds
I feel a hurricane
What?
Baby that is a lie
I'm a good girl
So you could open one the leader to the purple
Like a lightning board
Your heart will blow
Oh but it's time you'll know
You just gotta wake now come on
Feel it on
Her leg and
It's shining
Just like a lie
Like a fire
I'm dead
Oh no
Baby you're fine
You're alive
Don't want to die
Baby
You're alive
Because you shot
What's the scale
Baby you're fine
You're worth
Gone and you're cursed
You're alive
You're cursed
You're gonna leave the body
You're alive
Oh
Baby
It's always shining
You're
Now it's time to let it go
Stay out
Come on
Baby
You're alive
Because you're alive
Oh
Baby
You're worth
Gone and you're cursed
You're gonna leave the body
You're alive
Oh
Baby
You're alive
Oh
Baby
You're alive
Oh
Baby
You're alive
Oh
Baby
Thank you for all of your love
Thank you
One plus
We'll see you in the next time
Come on
Time to move